1. **WHO SHOULD READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**
    
    If you visit the GA Connector website located at [https://gaconnector.com](https://gaconnector.com/) (the “Website”) or use our services at [https://app.gaconnector.com](https://app.gaconnector.com/) (The Service), you should read this Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, share and process your personal data.
    
2. **WHO IS THE DATA CONTROLLER?**
    
    Business name: MarTech Solutions LLC  
    Business address: #12578, 8 The Green, Dover, DE, Kent, US, 19901  
    Contact email: [\[email protected\]](https://gaconnector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    
3. **WHAT INFORMATION DOES GA CONNECTOR APP COLLECT?**
    
    Visitors of the GA Connector website, [https://gaconnector.com](https://gaconnector.com/), and MarTech Solutions LLC clients using the GA Connector service (“The Service”)
    
    If you are a visitor to the Website or a MarTech Solutions LLC client who registers or signs into the Service via the Website (“Client”), we may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“MarTech Solutions LLC Client Information”), which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”):
    
    * Name
        
    * Email address
        
    * The domains domain of your website
        
    * The name of the CRM software you are using
        
    * Device information such as device model, device ID number
        
    * Browser settings and IP address
        
    * Information about your browsing activity on our website
        
    * Referral page from which you visited our website
        
    * Your behavior across different websites
        
    * Your financial details such as card number and bank name
        
    * Organisation you work for
        
4. **HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATA?**
    
    * **Data you voluntarily provide to us**
        
        When you fill out sign-up forms on our Website to use our Services, when you contact us, when you provide us with your email address, and when you make payment to us, you directly provide your personal data to us. 
        
    * **Data we automatically collect about you**
        
        When you visit our website, we collect certain categories of personal data automatically, by using various tools such as cookies and trackers. For instance, we use google analytics to collect your IP address data, your device identifier, and your referral page. 
        
5. **FOR WHAT PURPOSES DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**
    
    Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any or all of the following ways:
    
    * To provide you use of and access to our Website and the Service;
        
    * To operate, improve, and personalize our Website and the Service;
        
    * To provide you with customer service or customer support and to contact you to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems with your account;
        
    * To send periodic emails using the email address you provide to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
        
    * To process payment transactions.
        
    * To comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, security breaches, potentially prohibited or illegal activities and to protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
        
    * To enable our trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, to perform their obligations, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
        
    * In addition, we may provide certain information to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
        
6. **WHAT LEGAL B ASES DO WE RELY ON TO COLLECT AND USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**
    
    |     |     |     |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | **Categories of personal data** | **Purposes** | **Legal basis** |
    | Name, <br><br>Surname, <br><br>Business name, <br><br>The domains domain of your website<br><br>The name of the CRM software you’re using<br><br>Fİnancial information such as card details and bank informtion | To process payments, to provide our services, to enable you to use our services | Contractual necessity |
    | Device information, IP address and similar data collected through analytics and marketing cookies | To analyze website traffic, to serve targeted ads, to analyze user behaviour and to improve our website, and our services | Consent |
    | Email address | To send promotional emails | Consent |
    | All data collected and processed about you | To comply with applicable laws and regulations | Legal obligation |
    
7. **HOW DO WE ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**
    
    We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of Personally Identifiable Information and Client User Data when you submit the information.
    
    We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and is not stored.
    
    After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
    
8. **WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS IN RELATION TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**
    
    Under the EU and the UK GDPR, you are entitled to exercising the following data subject rights: 
    
    * Right of Access: You may submit a request to obtain copies of the personal data we hold about you and confirm if we process your data
        
    * Right to rectify your personal data: You may submit a request  for rectification of inaccuracies in your personal data
        
    * Right to Object to processing of your personal data: You can object to our processing of your personal data if we are relying on legitimate interest as the lawful ground for data processing; and
        
    * Right to Be Forgotten: You may (subject to the limitations set forth in the law applies) exercise your right to be forgotten 
        
    * Right to Data Portability: You can submit a request for your personal data to be transferred to another organization.
        
    * Right to Restriction: You may request to restrict the processing of your data because there is some disagreement about its accuracy or objections against its legitimate usage
        
9. **HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS**
    
    You can exercise your rights described above via the following ways:
    
    * Email: You can submit a request via email to to [\[email protected\]](https://gaconnector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will respond to your request upon verification of your identity within a reasonable period of time, and to the maximum extent practical.
        
    * Post: You can submit a request via post at: 
        
10. **DOES MarTech Solutions LLC DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?**
    
    We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Client User Data. MarTech Solutions LLC Client Information may be transferred to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release MarTech Solutions LLC Client Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable MarTech Solutions LLC Client Information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
    
    We may also disclose MarTech Solutions LLC Client Information, Client User Data and Personally Identifiable Information to allow for a change of ownership of MarTech Solutions LLC (including, but not limited to, an acquisition by or merger with another company) and related transfer of all such information to the new owner, in which case any information remains protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
    
11. **DATA RETENTION** 
    
    We retain your personal data for as long as it is necessary for the purposes for which your personal data is processed.
    
    When deciding on the data retention period, we take into account factors such as “legal obligations” we are subject to, “statutory retention periods”, “level of sensitivity of personal data”, and “purpose(s) for the collection and/or use of personal data.
    
12. **INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS**
    
    When we use Amazon Web Services to store your personal data, we transfer your personal data to a non-adequate country in the context of the GDPR.
    
    To comply with the GDPR’s international data transfer rules and to lawfully transfer your personal data abroad, we rely on and implement the Standard Contractual Clauses under article 46 GDPR ad we implement appropriate supplementary measures. 
    
13. **HOW TO FILE A COMPLAINT WITH SUPERVISORY AUTHORITIES**
    
    If you have any concerns or complaints in relation to the collection and use of your personal data, you can submit an official complaint to the relevant data protection authority.
    
    Please be noted that the complaint process may vary by the country in which you submit your request. You can refer to the following Directory to learn more about how to submit a complaint:

14. **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**
    
    If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
    
15. **CONTACTING US**
    
    If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.
    
    [\[email protected\]](https://gaconnector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
